say what does Jordan personally think
leads to prostate cancer in the standard
oh my gosh man I'd be speculating
honestly on that um we really have no
way to prove that because again look at
look at every variable in every
individual's life every single person
it's different every every one of us is
unique the way we live our lives is
pretty unique even though we're we're
all exposed to the similar stuff but in
different
ratios it's impossible to study that I
mean that this is where epidemiology and
things like that come in handy but they
never prove cause and effect you just
get a a lot of different speculations on
well it could be this it could be that
let's look at these Trends let's look at
these correlations um I don't know the
answer I will just say what I always
tell guys when they ask me like what can
I do to improve my prostate health or
lessen my chances of getting prostate
cancer I'm like the same thing you do to
uh reduce your risk of getting any
cancer is be as healthy as you can be
that's it and that includes looking at
the other things in your life that you
know crappy processed foods poisons
heavy metals exposure I mean who the
list is a mile long and that may even
still not reduce your chances of getting
prostate cancer maybe something else
unforeseen that happens that you don't
even know you're being exposed to um but
I definitely don't think it's hormonal
obviously I mean the majority of guys
that get prostate cancer have already
have low testosterone right um but yeah
I I wish I knew the answer to that one I
don't even fully understand cancer
anymore the more I research and look
into that stuff it's just a very
interesting topic you start looking at
the uh differences and even how how a
pathologist will Define what they think
is cancer and there's there's massive
disagreement even looking at a slide and
you start going how many people are
getting treated for cancers when they
don't actually have cancer like I mean
you don't know just from always looking
at a cell line under a microscope that
it's truly the c-word you know so you
know you got to go with your gut on a
lot of that stuff but I don't know the
direct cause
[Music]